<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<DataFeeds>
<Item>
  <ASIN>B000SFK3HC</ASIN>
  <SalesRank>6186</SalesRank>
  <SmallImage xmlns:aws="http://webservices.amazon.com/AWSECommerceService">
    <aws:URL>http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/511NpLhT8AL._SL75_.jpg</aws:URL>
    <aws:Height Units="pixels">75</aws:Height>
    <aws:Width Units="pixels">73</aws:Width>
  </SmallImage>
  <MediumImage xmlns:aws="http://webservices.amazon.com/AWSECommerceService">
    <aws:URL>http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/511NpLhT8AL._SL160_.jpg</aws:URL>
    <aws:Height Units="pixels">160</aws:Height>
    <aws:Width Units="pixels">156</aws:Width>
  </MediumImage>
  <LargeImage xmlns:aws="http://webservices.amazon.com/AWSECommerceService">
    <aws:URL>http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/511NpLhT8AL._SL500_.jpg</aws:URL>
    <aws:Height Units="pixels">500</aws:Height>
    <aws:Width Units="pixels">486</aws:Width>
  </LargeImage>
  <ItemAttributes>
    <BatteriesIncluded>1</BatteriesIncluded>
    <Binding>Wireless Phone Accessory</Binding>
    <Brand>Sony Ericsson</Brand>
    <Color>BLACK</Color>
    <EAN>0822248022428</EAN>
    <Feature>This is a tri-band GSM 900/1800/1900 cell phone with international 3G compatibility via 2100 MHz, and UMTS</Feature>
    <Feature>2-megapixel digital camera with 4x digital zoom and video capture</Feature>
    <Feature>Dedicated Walkman audio player with controls on front of slider phone</Feature>
    <Feature>Bluetooth wireless connectivity for hands-free headsets and music streaming</Feature>
    <Feature>Expandable memory via Memory Stick Pro Duo slot; up to 7 hours talk time</Feature>
    <ItemDimensions>
      <Height Units="hundredths-inches">380</Height>
      <Length Units="hundredths-inches">180</Length>
      <Width Units="hundredths-inches">80</Width>
    </ItemDimensions>
    <Label>Sony Ericsson Mobile</Label>
    <ListPrice>
      <Amount>34999</Amount>
      <CurrencyCode>USD</CurrencyCode>
      <FormattedPrice>$349.99</FormattedPrice>
    </ListPrice>
    <Manufacturer>Sony Ericsson Mobile</Manufacturer>
    <Model>W850i</Model>
    <MPN>822248022428</MPN>
    <PackageQuantity>1</PackageQuantity>
    <ProductGroup>Wireless</ProductGroup>
    <ProductTypeName>WIRELESS_ACCESSORY</ProductTypeName>
    <Publisher>Sony Ericsson Mobile</Publisher>
    <ReleaseDate>2007-08-10</ReleaseDate>
    <Studio>Sony Ericsson Mobile</Studio>
    <Title>Sony Ericsson W850i Unlocked Cell Phone with 2 MP Camera, 3G, MP3/Video Player, Memory Stick Duo/Pro Slot--International Version with Warranty (Black)</Title>
    <UPC>822248022428</UPC>
  </ItemAttributes>
  <EditorialReviews>
    <EditorialReview>
      <Source>Amazon.com Product Description</Source>
      <Content>After the success of the candybar-style W810i, Sony Ericsson went with a slider design for the W850i, which adds dedicated music control buttons to the front of the phone. This tri-band phone offers easy global connectivity as well as support for high-speed 3G (UMTS) internet access for fast connectivity to multimedia and downloadable games and applications. In addition to a powerful and easy-to-use Walkman music player, the W850i boasts a 2-megapixel auto-focus camera with flash, Memory Stick Duo expansion, Bluetooth connectivity for communication headsets and stereo headphones, an FM radio, and a speakerphone.   &lt;p&gt; &lt;table align=right width=500 cellpadding=10&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;img  src="http://images.amazon.com/images/G/01/wireless/detail-page/B000SFK3HC-w850i-trio.jpg" border=0  align=top&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dedicated music control buttons on the front of this slider phone make for easy listening. This phone also includes a 2-megapixel camera on the back.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/table&gt; This unlocked cell phone can be used with a GSM network service provider and it provides tri-band connectivity (900 MHz, 1800 MHz, 1900 MHz). It does not come with a SIM card, and it requires that you provide a SIM card for usage with your selected service provider. This phone comes with a one-year warranty from a third party provider. &lt;p&gt; The W850i is a 3G data-enabled device, compatible with third-generation mobile networks that offer broadband-like transfer speeds--up to 384 kbps--providing quick and easy access to audio and video streaming, Web surfing, multimedia messaging, and email wherever you go. This phone includes a secondary camera lens on the front that lets you use the W850i as a video phone. During a video call (placed to a compatible phone on a compatible network), you can see a live video stream of the person you're talking to and they can see you. When the only choice around is GSM, the P990i can hop onto a GPRS data link.  &lt;p&gt; The 2-inch screen sports a 240 x 320-pixel resolution with support for up to 256K colors. Below the screen resides soft navigation keys and recessed navigation buttons  as well as dedicated buttons for the Walkman digital audio player controls. Sliding the front of the phone up reveals the numeric keypad. The W850i contains 16 MB of embedded memory, which can be expanded via a Memory Stick Duo slot (which also supports Pro Duo cards), giving you storage capacities of 2 GB and beyond.  &lt;p&gt; The W850i's phone book can hold up to 1000 contacts with multiple entries per contact. A call list remembers your most recent missed, received and dialed calls. The phone's voice activated dialing makes calling your contacts as easy as saying their names, while the built-in speakerphone makes it easy to talk without having the phone to your ear. Polyphonic ringtones are included and you can also use MP3 and AAC music files as ringtones. A cool application called Music DJ even lets you mix your own ringtones. Meanwhile, picture caller ID lets you assign a photo to specific callers. Similarly, a ringer ID lets you assign ringtones to callers. For those times you want to keep things discreet, there's a vibrate ringer mode. &lt;p&gt; This phone provides Bluetooth version 2.0 wireless connectivity, and includes profiles for communication headset, handsfree car kits, and printing. You can connect your laptop (either via Bluetooth or wired USB) and enjoy dial-up networking (DUN)--surf the Internet, send email, and access files from a server. And with the A2DP Bluetooth profile, you can stream your music to a pair of compatible Bluetooth stereo headphones. In addition to USB and Bluetooth connectivity, this phone also has an infrared receiver for data synchronization. &lt;p&gt; Being that this is a Walkman phone, the W850i provides a great mobile music experience. Load up your favorite songs in MP3 or AAC format on a memory card and listen to your heart's content. The user-friendly music player application also includes a "Music Mode" that shuts down the phone functions so you can listen on an airplane or anytime you don't want to accept calls. Meanwhile, Digital Mega Bass and stereo widening combine to enhance your listening experience. There's even an FM radio for catching the big game or your favorite stations. The radio also supports reception of digital song information from radio stations. &lt;p&gt; The 2-megapixel camera includes a 4x digital zoom and integrated flash. Other camera features include a night mode, color effects, burst shoot mode, white balance settings, and four shutter sounds. It also captures video clips in QCIF format (176 x 144 pixels) that can be as long as your available memory will permit. You can also easily record video clips, and it comes with the VideoDJ feature that allows you to put together selected video clips and add sound to the clips. &lt;p&gt; If you're looking for a mobile productivity partner, the W850i has you covered. Support is built in for sending and receiving pictures, text, graphics, and sound via MMS messages. When used in combination with the phone's built-in still and video camera, MMS opens up a whole new world of messaging possibilities. T9 text entry, a technology that makes it easier for people to enter words and text on handsets, is built into the unit-- a plus for mobile email and text messaging users. &lt;p&gt; The phone also ships with a built-in email client with support for POP3 and IMAP4 protocols, while the included Access NetFront Web Browser allows you to surf full HTML web sites. The W850i also supports RSS feeds, allowing you to use your phone to view up-to-the-minute news and other content from selected Web sites and blogs. Just subscribe to the feed and let it come to you.  &lt;p&gt; A number of handy software tools are bundled with the W850i, including a voice memo recorder, a to-do list, a calculator, a calendar and an alarm clock. The phone also supports the SyncML PC synchronization standard, which lets you synchronize your PC-based calendar, contacts, notes and tasks with your W850i.  &lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt;Vital Statistics&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; The W850i measures  3.8 x 1.8 x 0.8 inches and weighs 4.1 ounces. It runs on the 900/1800/1900 MHz GSM/GPRS and 2100 MHz UMTS frequencies. Battery life is rated at 7 hours of digital talk time and 350 hours of standby time. This phone comes with a one-year warranty from a third party provider.</Content>
      <IsLinkSuppressed>0</IsLinkSuppressed>
    </EditorialReview>
    <EditorialReview>
      <Source>Product Description</Source>
      <Content>Uniquely crafted, the MOTORIZR features a thin, narrow slider form factor with familiar finishes, rich housing materials and a multi-model design for using the phone in both the open and closed positions. Appealing to the senses, this sleek new device boasts exceptional imaging, vivid color screen, enhanced music and global connectivity. By offering the desired functionality in a familiar, easy to use design, the MOTORIZR is the companion for effortless style and entertainment on-the-go. Thin, narrow slider with a multi-modal design and rich colors, materials and finish 2.0 MP camera with a fixed lens, full screen viewfinder with high intensity camera light, frame center and status icons Supported audio formats: MP3, AAC, AAC+, and AAC+ Enhanced 20 MB of on-board user memory and Micro SD memory slot for up to 2 GB of extra storage for music, pictures and other media USB 2.0 connectivity for file transfers and data access Video capture and playback Quad-Band (GPRS/EDGE) functionality Display: 1.9 inches, 176 x 220 TFT (262k colors)</Content>
    </EditorialReview>
  </EditorialReviews>
  <BrowseNodes>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>283278011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>GSM 900-1800-1900</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>283274011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>By Frequency</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>283273011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Unlocked Phones</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>301188</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Accessories</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>408234</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Categories</Name>
                      <Ancestors>
                        <BrowseNode>
                          <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                          <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                        </BrowseNode>
                      </Ancestors>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>283288011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Bluetooth</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>283287011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>By Type</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>283273011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Unlocked Phones</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>301188</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Accessories</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>408234</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Categories</Name>
                      <Ancestors>
                        <BrowseNode>
                          <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                          <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                        </BrowseNode>
                      </Ancestors>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>283289011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Camera</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>283287011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>By Type</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>283273011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Unlocked Phones</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>301188</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Accessories</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>408234</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Categories</Name>
                      <Ancestors>
                        <BrowseNode>
                          <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                          <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                        </BrowseNode>
                      </Ancestors>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>283291011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>MP3</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>283287011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>By Type</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>283273011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Unlocked Phones</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>301188</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Accessories</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>408234</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Categories</Name>
                      <Ancestors>
                        <BrowseNode>
                          <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                          <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                        </BrowseNode>
                      </Ancestors>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>283294011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Video</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>283287011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>By Type</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>283273011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Unlocked Phones</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>301188</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Accessories</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>408234</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Categories</Name>
                      <Ancestors>
                        <BrowseNode>
                          <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                          <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                        </BrowseNode>
                      </Ancestors>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>403835011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Everything Else</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>408234</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Categories</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>1245893011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Video</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>1245886011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Phone Features (feature_five_browse-bin)</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>388190011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Refinements</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>1245892011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Slider</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>1245886011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Phone Features (feature_five_browse-bin)</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>388190011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Refinements</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>1245888011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Camera</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>1245886011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Phone Features (feature_five_browse-bin)</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>388190011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Refinements</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>1245887011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Bluetooth</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>1245886011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Phone Features (feature_five_browse-bin)</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>388190011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Refinements</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>668706011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>GSM 900/1800/1900</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>616871011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Frequency (feature_browse-bin)</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>589313011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Browse Refinements</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>388190011</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Refinements</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>603009011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Video</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>603002011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Unlocked Phone Features (feature_three_browse-bin)</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>589313011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Browse Refinements</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>388190011</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Refinements</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>603008011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Slider</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>603002011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Unlocked Phone Features (feature_three_browse-bin)</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>589313011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Browse Refinements</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>388190011</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Refinements</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>603004011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Camera</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>603002011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Unlocked Phone Features (feature_three_browse-bin)</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>589313011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Browse Refinements</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>388190011</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Refinements</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>603003011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Bluetooth</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>603002011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Unlocked Phone Features (feature_three_browse-bin)</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>589313011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Browse Refinements</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>388190011</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Refinements</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>589315011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Sony Ericsson</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>589314011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Compatibility (feature_two_browse-bin)</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>589313011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Browse Refinements</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>388190011</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Refinements</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>754528</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Hot New Products</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>508494</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Special Features</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
  </BrowseNodes>
<PriceSummary>
  <AmazonPrice>
    <Amount>33171</Amount>
    <Availability>Usually ships in 1 to 2 months</Availability>
    <SalesRestriction/>
    <MerchantID>ATVPDKIKX0DER</MerchantID>
    <MerchantName>Amazon.com</MerchantName>
    <OfferListingID>VHOhFcr67U4rU0VUwSp9RAg6QUogMFqypYTspV6R%2FmgdMt6TxZ%2FKJJci%2B%2BPPr5WhUyInXMUNMzde2VwI%2BUf0CQ%3D%3D</OfferListingID>
    <ShippingCharge>
      <ShippingType>StandardShipping</ShippingType>
      <ShippingPrice>
        <Amount>0</Amount>
        <CurrencyCode>USD</CurrencyCode>
        <FormattedPrice>$0.00</FormattedPrice>
      </ShippingPrice>
    </ShippingCharge>
    <IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>1</IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>
    <IsEligibleForPrime>1</IsEligibleForPrime>
  </AmazonPrice>
  <BuyBoxPrice isAmazonOffer="true">
    <Amount>33171</Amount>
    <Availability>Usually ships in 1 to 2 months</Availability>
    <SalesRestriction/>
    <MerchantID>ATVPDKIKX0DER</MerchantID>
    <MerchantName>Amazon.com</MerchantName>
    <OfferListingID>VHOhFcr67U4rU0VUwSp9RAg6QUogMFqypYTspV6R%2FmgdMt6TxZ%2FKJJci%2B%2BPPr5WhUyInXMUNMzde2VwI%2BUf0CQ%3D%3D</OfferListingID>
    <ShippingCharge>
      <ShippingType>StandardShipping</ShippingType>
      <ShippingPrice>
        <Amount>0</Amount>
        <CurrencyCode>USD</CurrencyCode>
        <FormattedPrice>$0.00</FormattedPrice>
      </ShippingPrice>
    </ShippingCharge>
    <IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>1</IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>
    <IsEligibleForPrime>1</IsEligibleForPrime>
  </BuyBoxPrice>
  <FMPrice isAmazonOffer="true">
    <Amount>33171</Amount>
    <Availability>Usually ships in 1 to 2 months</Availability>
    <SalesRestriction/>
    <MerchantID>ATVPDKIKX0DER</MerchantID>
    <MerchantName>Amazon.com</MerchantName>
    <OfferListingID>VHOhFcr67U4rU0VUwSp9RAg6QUogMFqypYTspV6R%2FmgdMt6TxZ%2FKJJci%2B%2BPPr5WhUyInXMUNMzde2VwI%2BUf0CQ%3D%3D</OfferListingID>
    <ShippingCharge>
      <ShippingType>StandardShipping</ShippingType>
      <ShippingPrice>
        <Amount>0</Amount>
        <CurrencyCode>USD</CurrencyCode>
        <FormattedPrice>$0.00</FormattedPrice>
      </ShippingPrice>
    </ShippingCharge>
    <IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>1</IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>
    <IsEligibleForPrime>1</IsEligibleForPrime>
  </FMPrice>
  <ItemPrice>
    <Amount>33171</Amount>
    <Availability>Usually ships in 1 to 2 months</Availability>
    <SalesRestriction/>
    <MerchantID>ATVPDKIKX0DER</MerchantID>
    <MerchantName>Amazon.com</MerchantName>
    <OfferListingID>2nXDUYHhy69qd5%2B73zGv8GAl%2Fq9VQN3LR4953h%2FK%2FYm3L6%2FzLo6CDQiYzQ1GYV9OdM4DjG5OvOtEDbjtux%2Fapg%3D%3D</OfferListingID>
    <ShippingCharge>
      <ShippingType>StandardShipping</ShippingType>
      <ShippingPrice>
        <Amount>0</Amount>
        <CurrencyCode>USD</CurrencyCode>
        <FormattedPrice>$0.00</FormattedPrice>
      </ShippingPrice>
    </ShippingCharge>
    <IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>1</IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>
    <IsEligibleForPrime>1</IsEligibleForPrime>
  </ItemPrice>
</PriceSummary>
<Description>
  <Abstract>Buy Sony Ericsson W850i Unlocked Cell Phone with 2 MP Camera, 3G, MP3/Video Player, Memory Stick Duo/Pro Slot--International Version with Warranty (Black) from Amazon.com!</Abstract>
  <Promotion/>
  <AmazonUrl>http://www.amazon.com/dp/B000SFK3HC/ref=asc_df_B000SFK3HC700960/?tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=380333&amp;creativeASIN=B000SFK3HC&amp;linkCode=asn</AmazonUrl>
  <MarketplaceURL>http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B000SFK3HC/ref=asc_df_B000SFK3HC700960?s=merchant&amp;m=MERCHANTID_TO_REPLACE&amp;v=glance&amp;tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=380341&amp;linkCode=asn&amp;creativeASIN=B000SFK3HC</MarketplaceURL>
  <OfferUrl>http://www.amazon.com/gp/offer-listing/B000SFK3HC/ref=asc_df_B000SFK3HC700960?ie=UTF8&amp;condition=new&amp;tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=380345&amp;creativeASIN=B000SFK3HC&amp;linkCode=asm</OfferUrl>
  <Url>http://www.amazon.com/dp/B000SFK3HC/ref=asc_df_B000SFK3HC700960?tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=380337&amp;creativeASIN=B000SFK3HC&amp;linkCode=asn</Url>
  <UsedUrl>http://www.amazon.com/gp/offer-listing/B000SFK3HC/ref=asc_df_B000SFK3HC700960?ie=UTF8&amp;condition=used&amp;tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=380349&amp;creativeASIN=B000SFK3HC&amp;linkCode=asm</UsedUrl>
</Description>
</Item>
<Item>
  <ASIN>B000H84CFY</ASIN>
  <SalesRank>8388</SalesRank>
  <SmallImage xmlns:aws="http://webservices.amazon.com/AWSECommerceService">
    <aws:URL>http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/31FB0NWAX3L._SL75_.jpg</aws:URL>
    <aws:Height Units="pixels">75</aws:Height>
    <aws:Width Units="pixels">36</aws:Width>
  </SmallImage>
  <MediumImage xmlns:aws="http://webservices.amazon.com/AWSECommerceService">
    <aws:URL>http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/31FB0NWAX3L._SL160_.jpg</aws:URL>
    <aws:Height Units="pixels">160</aws:Height>
    <aws:Width Units="pixels">77</aws:Width>
  </MediumImage>
  <LargeImage xmlns:aws="http://webservices.amazon.com/AWSECommerceService">
    <aws:URL>http://ecx.images-amazon.com/images/I/31FB0NWAX3L._SL500_.jpg</aws:URL>
    <aws:Height Units="pixels">500</aws:Height>
    <aws:Width Units="pixels">241</aws:Width>
  </LargeImage>
  <ItemAttributes>
    <BatteriesIncluded>1</BatteriesIncluded>
    <Brand>Kyocera</Brand>
    <Color>Pearlized White</Color>
    <EAN>0836182002125</EAN>
    <Feature>Full Color Screen</Feature>
    <Feature>Mobile Web Browsing</Feature>
    <Feature>Text Messaging</Feature>
    <Feature>Two way speakerphone</Feature>
    <Feature>TTY/TDD enabled for the hearing impaired</Feature>
    <ItemDimensions>
      <Height Units="inches">2.6</Height>
      <Length Units="inches">11</Length>
      <Weight Units="hundredths-pounds">100</Weight>
      <Width Units="inches">7</Width>
    </ItemDimensions>
    <Label>KYOCERA</Label>
    <ListPrice>
      <Amount>1999</Amount>
      <CurrencyCode>USD</CurrencyCode>
      <FormattedPrice>$19.99</FormattedPrice>
    </ListPrice>
    <Manufacturer>KYOCERA</Manufacturer>
    <Model>Oystr</Model>
    <MPN>Oystr</MPN>
    <PackageDimensions>
      <Height Units="hundredths-inches">250</Height>
      <Length Units="hundredths-inches">1080</Length>
      <Weight Units="hundredths-pounds">90</Weight>
      <Width Units="hundredths-inches">600</Width>
    </PackageDimensions>
    <PackageQuantity>1</PackageQuantity>
    <ProductGroup>CE</ProductGroup>
    <ProductTypeName>CONSUMER_ELECTRONICS</ProductTypeName>
    <Publisher>KYOCERA</Publisher>
    <Studio>KYOCERA</Studio>
    <Title>Virgin Mobile Oyster Color Flip Phone - Pearlized White</Title>
    <UPC>836182002125</UPC>
  </ItemAttributes>
  <CustomerReviews>
    <AverageRating>3.0</AverageRating>
    <TotalReviews>49</TotalReviews>
    <TotalReviewPages>10</TotalReviewPages>
    <Review>
      <ASIN>B000H84CFY</ASIN>
      <Rating>5</Rating>
      <HelpfulVotes>0</HelpfulVotes>
      <CustomerId>A22BG7PWHZAIM</CustomerId>
      <Reviewer>
        <CustomerId>A22BG7PWHZAIM</CustomerId>
        <Name>M. Greene-Bennae</Name>
        <Nickname>networkmom</Nickname>
        <Location>Space Coast</Location>
      </Reviewer>
      <TotalVotes>0</TotalVotes>
      <Date>2008-12-26</Date>
      <Summary>I love this phone!</Summary>
      <Content>I love this phone almost 2 years old now and no problems! Virgin is great too! I have several! Great for kids: just do text: $10 a month! no contracts no fees! it's freedom!</Content>
    </Review>
    <Review>
      <ASIN>B000H84CFY</ASIN>
      <Rating>5</Rating>
      <HelpfulVotes>0</HelpfulVotes>
      <CustomerId>A1QKJXM9NB7FSR</CustomerId>
      <Reviewer>
        <CustomerId>A1QKJXM9NB7FSR</CustomerId>
        <Name>L. Burger</Name>
      </Reviewer>
      <TotalVotes>0</TotalVotes>
      <Date>2008-11-18</Date>
      <Summary>Great Little Phone... But don't pay more than $20</Summary>
      <Content>I bought the green version of this phone (was a Target Special, ~$18) about 2.5 years ago. This phone has been a gem. I've had no problems with battery life (lasts about a week on standby). However, I got the white version for both my parents and they did experience problems with battery life... I read somewhere that had to do with a specific version of the phone, unfortunately I don't remember the details. I use cell phones mainly to make calls on the run... I don't do text messaging,  the web, emails, etc... That's what computers are for in my world;) So the fact that this phone is really basic is a positive for me... I switched over to Virgin Mobile approximately 5 years ago, and I've been very pleased... I don't do much wireless calling, so paying by the minute has saved me hundreds of dollars per year versus my earlier contract deal with Sprint. I even got my parents (they're 70+) to switch over to Virgin... They also couldn't be happier.. We must be some of their oldest customers;)... This phone is $9.99 at Virgin's website, with free shipping... Don't pay a dime more.</Content>
    </Review>
    <Review>
      <ASIN>B000H84CFY</ASIN>
      <Rating>2</Rating>
      <HelpfulVotes>0</HelpfulVotes>
      <CustomerId>A20Q1ROFHUY91A</CustomerId>
      <Reviewer>
        <CustomerId>A20Q1ROFHUY91A</CustomerId>
        <Name>Sandoz</Name>
        <Location>Pgh, PA</Location>
      </Reviewer>
      <TotalVotes>0</TotalVotes>
      <Date>2008-09-17</Date>
      <Summary>Was a nice little phone....  UNTIL the display screen died</Summary>
      <Content>I finally gave in and joined the portable phone era when I bought my very first one in Fall of '06 (the Virgin Oyster).  There were only a handful of requirements I had for this purchase:  I wanted to stay to be able to contact and be contacted while away from my home; I wanted to be able to text message; and I wanted a service plan that didn't require a long-term contract or the purchase of huge block of time.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;The Oyster fulfilled all these requirements and proved to a sturdy and reliable tool...that is, until one day recently (about 20 months after I first bought it) the display screen suddenly disappeared and never came back.  The phone still turns on, and makes and receives calls, but needless to say, without access to the ability to read and navigate menus, I lost access to any texting capabilities and my contact list.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;Before i wrote this review, I read through some other user's reviews about this phone and two mentioned having encountered the same problem of the disappearing display screen.  It's such a shame, too, that Virgin couldn't manufacture a dependable and durable piece of technology because i would have remained a customer of theirs, but now I doubt I will when I replace this phone.  Sure, the argument might be made that it was only a $20 purchase, but VM was getting about $100 dollars a year from me for their service, and because they couldn't even make a product that lasted for at least two years, now they won't.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;So if you are already own one of these phones, take this notice as a warning to be sure and copy your contact numbers, and either copy or forward any text messages you might want to save.</Content>
    </Review>
    <Review>
      <ASIN>B000H84CFY</ASIN>
      <Rating>3</Rating>
      <HelpfulVotes>1</HelpfulVotes>
      <CustomerId>A1G2TA7JB7N7JJ</CustomerId>
      <Reviewer>
        <CustomerId>A1G2TA7JB7N7JJ</CustomerId>
        <Name>Melissa M.</Name>
        <Location>Milwaukee, WI</Location>
      </Reviewer>
      <TotalVotes>1</TotalVotes>
      <Date>2008-07-19</Date>
      <Summary>Pretty decent phone</Summary>
      <Content>If I could give it 3.5, I would.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;I've had this phone since August 2006.  It was my first cell phone at age 18.  I can't afford a plan, so the prepaid plan works for me.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;The phone works great for me.  But I have 2 problems.  First, the battery life is not that great.  If I leave my phone on all night, when I wake up, I have low to no battery life left.  My second problem with the phone is how the ringtones sound.  I have bought so many ringtones of songs I like.  They sound great online of course, but then I play them on my phone and they sound like crap.  I do have some ringtones that sound great still, have static though it isn't a big deal.  However, for example, all my Evanescence ringtones don't come out right.  
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;It is a good phone though.  The graphics are great and it has really good features.  I just wish it came in other colors or was slimmer.  It is too lumpy in my pockets.  (I will admit I want another phone, one that is purple and has a camera, but those all have plans attached.  Bummer)  Though the phone does the job.</Content>
    </Review>
    <Review>
      <ASIN>B000H84CFY</ASIN>
      <Rating>3</Rating>
      <HelpfulVotes>0</HelpfulVotes>
      <CustomerId>A2JD4WAYOS66VP</CustomerId>
      <Reviewer>
        <CustomerId>A2JD4WAYOS66VP</CustomerId>
        <Name>L. L. Block</Name>
        <Location>Florida</Location>
      </Reviewer>
      <TotalVotes>0</TotalVotes>
      <Date>2008-06-22</Date>
      <Summary>Virgin Mobile....terrible customer service</Summary>
      <Content>Virgin mobile deactivated 4 of my phones and never notified me. I had changed a credit card which was excepted on line on a MOnday and on Tuesday I tried to make a call and found out they turned off all of my phones. I called my credit card company and they said my card was fine and don't know why Virgin Mobile did this. I went back and forth with Virgin and even asked for them to take a different card and they refused. I said then connect me to customer service and they said I had to email them. It would take 24 to 72 hours to resolve this. I emailed several customer care and was told to call Virgin again. I thought they were crazy. I called and once again was told I couldn't do anything about it. So again another email and a return with the same answer. Finally I received a email a week later at a address called charge back,she asked what she could do and I said please send my credit card info back. Well it was done and I was never notified and they only activated one phone. I have 3 dead phones with a lot of money in them. I wouldn't go with this company because if anything ever goes wrong with your account it will take at least a month to resolve it. I am now with a different cell phone company and still trying to get these 3 other phones turned on so I can use up my minutes. I have over $300. invested in this company.
&lt;br /&gt;</Content>
    </Review>
  </CustomerReviews>
  <EditorialReviews>
    <EditorialReview>
      <Source>Product Description</Source>
      <Content>A full-color screen, real music ringtones, mobile Web, downloadable games, and more.</Content>
    </EditorialReview>
    <EditorialReview>
      <Source>Amazon.com Product Description</Source>
      <Content>The Kyocera Oystr Prepaid Phone offers a full-color screen, text messaging, two-way speakerphone, Virgin's Superphonic ringtones and web browsing capabilities. On top of all that, the Oystr has a stylish look, making it an ideal first handset for anyone who wants to make a statement as they talk.&lt;P&gt;  &lt;table align=right width=216 cellpadding=10&gt; 		&lt;tr&gt; 		&lt;td&gt; &lt;img src="http://images.amazon.com/images/G/01/wireless/detail-page/oystr-1.jpg" border=0 align=top&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Oystr is an ideal first phone for those who want a stylish, affordable handset. View phone demo.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;small&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;  &lt;B&gt;Design&lt;/B&gt;&lt;br&gt; This black and white beauty offers a traditional clamshell design with a 65,000-color display and 128 x 128 pixel resolution. Most and on-screen menus are controlled by a five-way center button on the handset's control pad. Meanwhile, the top right side of the unit houses an extendable antenna while data and charging ports are housed on the unit's bottom edge. Up and down keys for volume control are provided on the left side of the phone.&lt;p&gt;  &lt;B&gt;Calling Features&lt;/B&gt;&lt;br&gt; The Oystr's built-in address book offers quick and easy management of your contacts. The phone comes with built-in Virgin Mobile "superphonic" ringtones plus a vibrating alert. Superphonic ringtones feature real music tracks and more are available via Virgin Mobile's download service. Voice dialing of up to ten contacts is supported, as are voice commands, so you can both dial numbers and control certain functions of the phone without ever touching it.&lt;p&gt;  &lt;b&gt;Messaging, Internet and Tools&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; The Oystr covers the messaging basics with support for sending and receiving text and picture messages easily and quickly (Virgin Mobile text messaging charges apply). eZitext text entry, which is a technology that makes it easier for people to enter words and text on handsets, is built into the unit-- a plus for mobile email and text messaging users.&lt;p&gt;  The phone fully supports Virgin Mobile's enhanced wireless content service, VirginXL. Use the pay-per-use service to download superphonic ringtones, animations and voices from MTV, Comedy central and the hottest recording artists. Get content and vote in TV-based polls via the MTV area of your phone, or get jokes and updates from Comedy Central. Pick a celebrity voice to answer your voicemail, or get a Sponge Bob thought of the day. The Oystr also supports mobile instant messaging via AIM.&lt;p&gt;  The Oyster ships with a number of handy tools including a calendar, a calculator with a tip calculator, an alarm clock, and a voice memo recorder.&lt;p&gt;  &lt;B&gt;Entertainment&lt;/B&gt; &lt;br&gt; The phone boasts custom Virgin Mobile graphics-- screen savers, wallpaper and menu icons-- that let you dress up your phone to suit your personality. More graphics, wallpapers and screensavers are available from the VirginXL service. The Oystr supports gaming, too, and a big selection of games can be downloaded from the VirginXL service.&lt;p&gt;  &lt;B&gt;Vital Statistics&lt;/B&gt; &lt;br&gt; The Kyocera Oystr weighs 3.5 ounces and measures 4.46 x 1.88 x .98 inches. Its lithium-ion battery is rated at up to 3.5 hours of digital talk time, and up to 175 hours of digital standby time. It runs on the CDMA 1900 frequency. The phone comes with a one year limited warranty.</Content>
      <IsLinkSuppressed>1</IsLinkSuppressed>
    </EditorialReview>
  </EditorialReviews>
  <BrowseNodes>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>172606</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Telephones &amp; Accessories</Name>
      <Children>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>172611</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Answering Devices</Name>
        </BrowseNode>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>11038701</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Audio Conferencing</Name>
        </BrowseNode>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>172746</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Corded Telephones</Name>
        </BrowseNode>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>172614</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Cordless Telephones</Name>
        </BrowseNode>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>229190</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Novelty Telephones</Name>
        </BrowseNode>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>11038691</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>PBX Phones &amp; Systems</Name>
        </BrowseNode>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>172621</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Pagers</Name>
        </BrowseNode>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>280352</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Video Phones</Name>
        </BrowseNode>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>13431611</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>VoIP</Name>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Children>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>172574</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Office Electronics</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>493964</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Categories</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>172282</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Electronics</Name>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>301330</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Kyocera</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>301216</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Manufacturers</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>301187</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Cell Phones with Service</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>408234</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Categories</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>1067706</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>All</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>301366</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Type</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>301187</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Cell Phones with Service</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>408234</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Categories</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>465604</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Flip</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>301187</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Cell Phones with Service</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>408234</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Categories</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>1200634</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Virgin Mobile</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>14001751</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Prepaid</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>301187</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Cell Phones with Service</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>408234</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Categories</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>240567011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Home Office Electronics</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>240560011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Electronics</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>1079730</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Categories</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>1079726</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Target</Name>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>295859011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Teen Girl (13-17)</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>295855011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>For Kids &amp; Teens</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>293862011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Wireless Accessories Gifting Store</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>251275011</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Custom Stores</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>551318</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Specialty Stores</Name>
                      <Ancestors>
                        <BrowseNode>
                          <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                          <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                        </BrowseNode>
                      </Ancestors>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>295858011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Teen Boy (13-17)</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>295855011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>For Kids &amp; Teens</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>293862011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Wireless Accessories Gifting Store</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>251275011</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Custom Stores</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>551318</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Specialty Stores</Name>
                      <Ancestors>
                        <BrowseNode>
                          <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
                          <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
                        </BrowseNode>
                      </Ancestors>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>754528</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>Hot New Products</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>508494</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Special Features</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>301185</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>Cell Phones &amp; Service</Name>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
    <BrowseNode>
      <BrowseNodeId>1245719011</BrowseNodeId>
      <Name>2005</Name>
      <Ancestors>
        <BrowseNode>
          <BrowseNodeId>1245718011</BrowseNodeId>
          <Name>Update Year</Name>
          <Ancestors>
            <BrowseNode>
              <BrowseNodeId>1232381011</BrowseNodeId>
              <Name>GPS Units</Name>
              <Ancestors>
                <BrowseNode>
                  <BrowseNodeId>15786581</BrowseNodeId>
                  <Name>Refinements</Name>
                  <Ancestors>
                    <BrowseNode>
                      <BrowseNodeId>172282</BrowseNodeId>
                      <Name>Electronics</Name>
                    </BrowseNode>
                  </Ancestors>
                </BrowseNode>
              </Ancestors>
            </BrowseNode>
          </Ancestors>
        </BrowseNode>
      </Ancestors>
    </BrowseNode>
  </BrowseNodes>
<PriceSummary>
  <ItemPrice>
    <Amount>2300</Amount>
    <Availability>Usually ships in 1-2 business days</Availability>
    <SalesRestriction/>
    <MerchantID>A17YQLTO1I1Y1L</MerchantID>
    <MerchantName>Island Bargains</MerchantName>
    <OfferListingID>YdOZz5o1gc0F4bbPn4Ym3omGal6Lt7dJtPMOVSo6mSKhnak5jzdbDq%2BTsd3vz9Xwy%2BxpBgu5MHzPLsk%2FwlvhOcmNzkwtr5xz0t1s4Tuu2GjGV%2FmQCLfFSv3jksLRO1XBx7SUbdQOYkE%3D</OfferListingID>
    <ShippingCharge>
      <ShippingPrice>
        <FormattedPrice>Check Site.</FormattedPrice>
      </ShippingPrice>
    </ShippingCharge>
    <IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>0</IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>
    <IsEligibleForPrime>0</IsEligibleForPrime>
  </ItemPrice>
  <MPPrice type="merchant">
    <Amount>2300</Amount>
    <Availability>Usually ships in 1-2 business days</Availability>
    <SalesRestriction/>
    <MerchantID>A17YQLTO1I1Y1L</MerchantID>
    <MerchantName>Island Bargains</MerchantName>
    <OfferListingID>YdOZz5o1gc0F4bbPn4Ym3omGal6Lt7dJtPMOVSo6mSKhnak5jzdbDq%2BTsd3vz9Xwy%2BxpBgu5MHzPLsk%2FwlvhOcmNzkwtr5xz0t1s4Tuu2GjGV%2FmQCLfFSv3jksLRO1XBx7SUbdQOYkE%3D</OfferListingID>
    <ShippingCharge>
      <ShippingPrice>
        <FormattedPrice>Check Site.</FormattedPrice>
      </ShippingPrice>
    </ShippingCharge>
    <IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>0</IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>
    <IsEligibleForPrime>0</IsEligibleForPrime>
  </MPPrice>
  <MPPrice type="merchant">
    <Amount>2381</Amount>
    <Availability>Usually ships in 1-2 business days</Availability>
    <SalesRestriction/>
    <MerchantID>APHG04RC9JV4W</MerchantID>
    <MerchantName>joelyust</MerchantName>
    <OfferListingID>Iv7geTR8G67idzM54ez7at7QkOcqFCiOEHEdHybC2ohKGYKfBIZ9FEAmnWqeL9yE2JoiDX0ktHQO%2F%2Br8Vd0yLwJZ04rwa0yHjDFD05Vi34S7nEOq3cgpKf9XfC6tO%2BNLefMLPtrvnQs%3D</OfferListingID>
    <ShippingCharge>
      <ShippingType>StandardShipping</ShippingType>
      <ShippingPrice>
        <Amount>499</Amount>
        <CurrencyCode>USD</CurrencyCode>
        <FormattedPrice>$4.99</FormattedPrice>
      </ShippingPrice>
    </ShippingCharge>
    <IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>0</IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>
    <IsEligibleForPrime>0</IsEligibleForPrime>
  </MPPrice>
  <MPPrice type="merchant">
    <Amount>6499</Amount>
    <Availability>Usually ships in 1-2 business days</Availability>
    <SalesRestriction/>
    <MerchantID>A3CYMS7CHHZ2LY</MerchantID>
    <MerchantName>Your Lowest Price</MerchantName>
    <OfferListingID>HEgu%2BRqt%2BZCQdkENrLpXlAxIpHL78cQou5wiR%2BJk3CgYbG59xAXRe1wSCn1BP5eVQiGTQY%2FlKMsXyzRe2sqNRhpg5S8RK9OmPw1dkOHAjAvcKFclxXcoSkMhbdk0%2BN6GnHVFj%2BVnqrHAGx6ebVbwIw%3D%3D</OfferListingID>
    <ShippingCharge>
      <ShippingType>StandardShipping</ShippingType>
      <ShippingPrice>
        <Amount>0</Amount>
        <CurrencyCode>USD</CurrencyCode>
        <FormattedPrice>$0.00</FormattedPrice>
      </ShippingPrice>
    </ShippingCharge>
    <IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>0</IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>
    <IsEligibleForPrime>0</IsEligibleForPrime>
  </MPPrice>
  <ThirdPartyNewPrice>
    <Amount>2300</Amount>
    <Availability>Usually ships in 1-2 business days</Availability>
    <SalesRestriction/>
    <MerchantID>A17YQLTO1I1Y1L</MerchantID>
    <MerchantName>Island Bargains</MerchantName>
    <OfferListingID>YdOZz5o1gc0F4bbPn4Ym3omGal6Lt7dJtPMOVSo6mSKhnak5jzdbDq%2BTsd3vz9Xwy%2BxpBgu5MHzPLsk%2FwlvhOcmNzkwtr5xz0t1s4Tuu2GjGV%2FmQCLfFSv3jksLRO1XBx7SUbdQOYkE%3D</OfferListingID>
    <ShippingCharge>
      <ShippingPrice>
        <FormattedPrice>Check Site.</FormattedPrice>
      </ShippingPrice>
    </ShippingCharge>
    <IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>0</IsEligibleForSuperSaverShipping>
    <IsEligibleForPrime>0</IsEligibleForPrime>
  </ThirdPartyNewPrice>
  <ThirdPartyUsedPrice>
    <Amount>1996</Amount>
    <Availability>In Stock</Availability>
    <SalesRestriction/>
    <ShippingCharge>
      <ShippingPrice>
        <FormattedPrice>Check Site.</FormattedPrice>
      </ShippingPrice>
    </ShippingCharge>
  </ThirdPartyUsedPrice>
</PriceSummary>
<Description>
  <Abstract>Buy Virgin Mobile Oyster Color Flip Phone - Pearlized White from Amazon.com!</Abstract>
  <Promotion/>
  <AmazonUrl>http://www.amazon.com/dp/B000H84CFY/ref=asc_df_B000H84CFY700960/?tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=380333&amp;creativeASIN=B000H84CFY&amp;linkCode=asn</AmazonUrl>
  <MarketplaceURL>http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B000H84CFY/ref=asc_df_B000H84CFY700960?s=merchant&amp;m=MERCHANTID_TO_REPLACE&amp;v=glance&amp;tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=380341&amp;linkCode=asn&amp;creativeASIN=B000H84CFY</MarketplaceURL>
  <OfferUrl>http://www.amazon.com/gp/offer-listing/B000H84CFY/ref=asc_df_B000H84CFY700960?ie=UTF8&amp;condition=new&amp;tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=380345&amp;creativeASIN=B000H84CFY&amp;linkCode=asm</OfferUrl>
  <Url>http://www.amazon.com/dp/B000H84CFY/ref=asc_df_B000H84CFY700960?tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=380337&amp;creativeASIN=B000H84CFY&amp;linkCode=asn</Url>
  <UsedUrl>http://www.amazon.com/gp/offer-listing/B000H84CFY/ref=asc_df_B000H84CFY700960?ie=UTF8&amp;condition=used&amp;tag=INSERT_TAG_HERE&amp;creative=380349&amp;creativeASIN=B000H84CFY&amp;linkCode=asm</UsedUrl>
</Description>
</Item>
</DataFeeds>
